A Guide to the Rockefeller University records, President, Frederick Seitz FA1069
Rockefeller Archive Center
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - Harvard University (Seitz), 1966-1968 (Box 109, Folder 12)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - Institutions, Associations, Individuals - Harvard University, 1964 (Box 109, Folder 13)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - Institutions, Associations, Individuals - Guggenheim Memorial Foundation, 1966 (Box 109, Folder 14)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - Hertz Foundation Award Nominations, 1968 (Box 109, Folder 15)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - Institutions, Associations, Individuals - Hertz Foundation - Awards for Achievement, 1965 (Box 109, Folder 16)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - Institutions, Associations, Individuals - High Energy Physics Association - Proposed, 1965 (Box 109, Folder 17)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - Institutions, Associations, Individuals - Honeywell Inc. Eng. And Science Award Committee, 1967 (Box 109, Folder 18)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - Illinois State Geological Survey, 1967 (Box 109, Folder 19)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - Illinois Science Advisory Council, 1968 (Box 109, Folder 20)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - Illinois Science Advisory Council, 1967 (Box 109, Folder 21)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - Illinois Science Advisory Council Report, 1967 (Box 109, Folder 22)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - Du Pont de Nemours and Company (Seitz), 1966-1968 (Box 109, Folder 23)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - Defense Science Board, 1969 (Box 109, Folder 24)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - Defense Science Board, 1966-1968 (Box 109, Folder 25)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - Seitz - Department of Defense (DOD) Personnel Forms (Box 109, Folder 26)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - Education and World Affairs, 1967-1968 (Box 109, Folder 27-28)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - Education and World Affairs - Board of Trustees Minutes (Box 109, Folder 29)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - Institutions, Associations, Individuals - Education and World Affairs - General, 1963 (Box 109, Folder 30)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - Institutions, Associations, Individuals - Education and World Affairs - Board of Trustees Meetings, 1963 (Box 109, Folder 31)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - Institutions, Associations, Individuals - Education and World Affairs - Certificate of Incorporation and By-Laws, 1962 (Box 109, Folder 32)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - Institutions, Associations, Individuals - Education and World Affairs - Board of Trustees Meetings, 1962 (Box 109, Folder 33)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - Institutions, Associations, Individuals - Franklin Institute, 1965-1966 (Box 109, Folder 34-35)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - Institutions, Associations, Individuals - Institute for the Future, 1967 (Box 110, Folder 1)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - Institutions, Associations, Individuals - International Club of Washington Inc., 1964 (Box 110, Folder 2)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - Oak Ridge Associated University - Monthly Highlights, Reports, 1970 (Box 110, Folder 3)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - International Association for Cultural Freedom, 1968 (Box 110, Folder 4)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - Invitations, 1968-1969 (Box 110, Folder 5)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - L. S. B. Leakey Foundation, 1969 (Box 110, Folder 6)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - Institutions, Associations, Individuals - Lincoln Academy of Illinois, 1964, 1966-1967 (Box 110, Folder 7-8)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - Institutions, Associations, Individuals - Midwestern University Research Association, 1963 (Box 110, Folder 9)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - National Academy of Engineering, 1963, 1968 (Box 110, Folder 10-11)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - Industrial Research Inc. - I-R Competition, 1968 (Box 110, Folder 12)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - Industrial Research Inc. (Seitz), 1968 (Box 110, Folder 13)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - Institutions, Associations, Individuals - Institute for Defense Analyses, 1964-1966 (Box 110, Folder 14-16)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - Institute for the The Future - General, 1968-1969 (Box 110, Folder 17-18)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - Minutes and Documents, 1968 (Box 110, Folder 19)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - Citizens Exchange Corps, 1968 (Box 110, Folder 20)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - Seitz - Citizens Committee for Peace with Freedom in Vietnam, 1967-1969 (Box 110, Folder 21)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - Civil Defense Forum, 1966 (Box 110, Folder 22)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - Consortium of Universities of Washingon Metro Area, 1967-1968 (Box 110, Folder 23)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - Du Pont, 1969 (Box 110, Folder 24)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - Institutions, Associations, Individuals - Graduate Research Center of the Southwest, 1965 (Box 110, Folder 25)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - Institutions, Associations, Individuals - Argonne Universities Association, 1965 (Box 110, Folder 26)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - Institutions, Associations, Individuals - Aspen Institute for Humanistic Studies, 1967 (Box 110, Folder 27)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - Institutions, Associations, Individuals - Associated Midwestern Universities, 1966 (Box 110, Folder 28-29)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - Institutions, Associations, Individuals - Associated Universities Inc., 1965 (Box 110, Folder 30)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - Institutions, Associations, Individuals - Association of American University Presses, 1964 (Box 110, Folder 31)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - Institutions, Associations, Individuals - American Physical Society, 1962-1966 (Box 110, Folder 32-36)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - Institutions, Associations, Individuals - Argonne Universities Association, 1966 (Box 110, Folder 37)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - Institutions, Associations, Individuals - American Institute of Physics, 1965 (Box 110, Folder 38)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - Institutions, Associations, Individuals - American Institute of Physics, 1963-1964 (Box 111, Folder 1)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - Amer Machine and Foundry (Seitz), 1965-1968 (Box 111, Folder 2)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - American Physical Society (APS) - Minutes, Council Meetings, 1969 (Box 111, Folder 3)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - Institutions, Associations, Individuals - American Physical Society (APS), 1967 (Box 111, Folder 4)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - Institutions, Associations, Individuals - American Physical Society (APS) - Council Meetings, 1966-1967 (Box 111, Folder 5)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - Institutions, Associations, Individuals - American Physical Society (APS) - Constitution and By-Laws Revision, 1966 (Box 111, Folder 6)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - AIP - Financial Statements, 1968 (Box 111, Folder 7)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - AIP - General, 1967-1968 (Box 111, Folder 8)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - AIP - Governing Board, 1967-1968 (Box 111, Folder 9)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - AIP - Minutes - Executive Committee and Governing Board, 1967-1968 (Box 111, Folder 10)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - AIP - Publication Charges, 1968 (Box 111, Folder 11)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - American Institute of Physics (AIP), 1966-1967 (Box 111, Folder 12-14)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - Academic Press "Solid State Physics" - Correspondence, 1964, 1968-1969 (Box 111, Folder 15-17)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - Aeroject General Corporation, 1967 (Box 111, Folder 18)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - Institutions, Associations, Individuals - American Institute of Aeronautics and Astronautics - Committee for Goddard Prize, 1964 (Box 111, Folder 19)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - AIP - Minutes - Executive Committee and Governing Board, 1969 (Box 111, Folder 20)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - AIP - Corporate Associates, 1968 (Box 111, Folder 21)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - AIP - Correspondence, 1967-1968 (Box 111, Folder 22)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - AIP - Financial Statements, 1969 (Box 111, Folder 23)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - Volunteer for International Assistance (VITA) Report, 1967-1968 (Box 111, Folder 24-26)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - Institutions, Associations, Individuals - Volunteers for International Tech Assistance, 1966-1967 (Box 111, Folder 27-28)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - Washington Academy of Sciences, 1967 (Box 111, Folder 29)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - Seitz - Chemistry Nominations (Box 111, Folder 30)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - Seitz - Behavioral Nominations (Box 111, Folder 31-32)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - Math Nominations (Seitz) (Alan T. Waterman Award), 1977-1978 (Box 112, Folder 1)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - MKW-Industry (Seitz) (Alan T. Waterman Award), 1977-1978 (Box 112, Folder 2)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - Biographical and Social Nominations (Seitz) (Alan T. Waterman Award), 1977-1978 (Box 112, Folder 3)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - Seitz - Engineering Nominations, 1977-1978 (Box 112, Folder 4)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - Washington Center for Metropolitan Studies, 1968 (Box 112, Folder 5)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - Institutions, Associations, Individuals - Washington Center for Metropolitan Studies, 1962-1963, 1966-1967 (Box 112, Folder 6-8)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - Welch Foundation, 1964-1966 (Box 112, Folder 9)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - Universities Research Association, 1969 (Box 112, Folder 10)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - Universities Association, Space Research Correspondence, 1967-1969 (Box 112, Folder 11-13)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - VITA - Minutes, Reports, Briefings, 1968 (Box 112, Folder 14)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - VITA - Correspondence, 1968 (Box 112, Folder 15)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - VITA - General Information, 1966 (Box 112, Folder 16)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - Institutions, Associations, Individuals - United Aircraft Corp., 1964-1966 (Box 112, Folder 17-20)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - Institutions, Associations, Individuals - United Aircraft Corp., 1963 (Box 113, Folder 1)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - Institutions, Associations, Individuals - University of Chicago - Argonne National Lab, 1965 (Box 113, Folder 2)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - Institutions, Associations, Individuals - University of Chicago - Argonne National Lab, 1964 (Box 113, Folder 3)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - Institutions, Associations, Individuals - University of Chicago, 1963 (Box 113, Folder 4)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - University of Illinois, 1968 (Box 113, Folder 5)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - Seitz - University of Illinois, 1966-1967 (Box 113, Folder 6)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - Seitz - University of Illinois, 1964 (Box 113, Folder 7)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - Institutions, Associations, Individuals - University of Illinois, 1963-1964 (Box 113, Folder 8-9)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - Research Corporation - Financial Statements and Reports, 1968 (Box 113, Folder 10)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - Research Corporation - General Information, 1967-1968 (Box 113, Folder 11-13)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - Rockefeller Foundation (Seitz), 1966 (Box 113, Folder 14)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - Institutions, Associations, Individuals - Rockefeller Foundation - Board of Trustees - Meetings, 1964 (Box 113, Folder 15)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - Institutions, Associations, Individuals - Rockefeller Foundation - Board of Trustees - General, 1964 (Box 113, Folder 16)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - Institutions, Associations, Individuals - Rockefeller Foundation - General, 1964 (Box 113, Folder 17)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - Science Service, 1967-1968 (Box 113, Folder 18)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - Security Forms (Box 113, Folder 19)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - Sloan Kettering Institute for Cancer Research, 1969 (Box 113, Folder 20)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - Speeches Lists, 1962-1969 (Box 113, Folder 21)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - Stanford University, 1968 (Box 113, Folder 22)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - United Aircraft - Abstracts and Reports, 1970 January-June (Box 113, Folder 23)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - United Aircraft - Correspondence, 1969 (Box 113, Folder 24)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - United Aircraft - Abstracts and Reports, 1969 (Box 113, Folder 25)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - United Aircraft, 1968 (Box 113, Folder 26)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - United Aircraft Research Laboratories Report, 1968 (Box 113, Folder 27)
- National Academy of Sciences Presidential Papers - United Aircraft, 1967 (Box 113, Folder 28)
- Traditional Chinese Medicine, 1970 (Box 114, Folder 1-3)
- 1973 Berkner Memorial (Box 115, Folder 1)
- 1973 Book Review for Amer. Scientist (Bromley) (Box 115, Folder 2)
- 1973 NSF Report of Survey team on Ultrasonic Imaging (Box 115, Folder 3)
- 1973 Georgetown University Panel - US Military Research and Development (Seitz and Rwn) (Box 115, Folder 4)
- 1973 CFR Elihu Root Series (Seitz introduction to Carrol Wilson) (Box 115, Folder 5)
- 1973 National Strategy and Information Center - Research and Development Prospects for International Security (Seitz and RWN) (Box 115, Folder 6)
- 1972 Battelle, Columbus, OH - Seitz Chapter (Book Published in 1973) (Box 115, Folder 7)
- 1971 Foreward by Seitz in Topics in Modern Physics: A Tribute to Edward U. Condon (Box 115, Folder 8)
- 1971 Naval Research Laboratory 50th Anniversary, Seitz Lecture, 1971 October 2 (Box 115, Folder 9)
- 1971 Electrochemical Society - Science and the University (Box 115, Folder 10)
- 1971 UMSCHAU - Seitz article (in German), 1971 February 18 (Box 115, Folder 11)
- 1972 Research Management - March Issue (SST article, Battelle, Seattle), 1971 (Box 115, Folder 12)
- 1972 University of Illinois - A Scientist Views Technology (Box 115, Folder 13)
- 1972 Institute of International Education Anniversary Dinner - Seitz Remarks (Box 115, Folder 14)
- 1972 American Educator Encyclopedia (Box 115, Folder 15)
- 1972 Enclyclopedia Americana Solid State Physics article by Seitz (Box 115, Folder 16)
- 1972 UMSCHAU - Seitz Forward, Series on American Universities (Box 115, Folder 17)
- 1970-1971 Encyclopedia of Education (Box 115, Folder 18)
- 1971 Seitz Introduction to Lecture - Science and Evolution of Public Policy (J. A. Shannon) (Box 115, Folder 19)
- 1971 McGraw Hill - Encyclopedia of Science and Technology and Yearbook (Box 115, Folder 20)
- 1971 Brussels-Irsia (Box 115, Folder 21)
- 1971 Puerto Rico, American Chemical Society (Box 115, Folder 22)
- 1971 Book Review for American Scientist (Logdson, MIT) (Box 115, Folder 23)
- 1971 AIP 40th Anniversary (Box 115, Folder 24)
- 1971 Symposium Sponsored by Poly. Inst. Brooklyn, Aspen Institute, Hudson Institute, 1971 November 17 (Box 115, Folder 25)
- 1971 Wigner Retirement Tribute, Princeton May 1, 1971, Physics Today, 1972 October, 1971-1972 (Box 115, Folder 26)
- 1971 Hugh Dryden Tribute as National Academy of Sciences (Box 115, Folder 27)
- 1971 SST Manuscript Battelle, Seattle (Box 115, Folder 28)
- Pending - Papers, Articles, 1973-1974 (Box 115, Folder 29)
- 1970 Book - Seitz Chapter - Science and Technology in World of Future (Box 115, Folder 30)
- 1970 AAPSS, Philadelphia (Box 115, Folder 31)
- 1970 Astronautics and Aeronautics (Box 115, Folder 32)
- 1970 Seton Hall University, South Orange, NJ, 1970 February 3 (Box 115, Folder 33)
- 1970 Nebraska Wesleyan University - Seitz gave Commencement Address (Box 115, Folder 34)
- 1970 Munich Lecture at Siemans Stiftung, 1970 December 7 (Box 115, Folder 35)
- 1970 Goucher College (Box 115, Folder 36)
- 1970 Cornell Medical College and Nursing School - Commencement Address (Box 115, Folder 37)
- 1969 St. Louis University Commencement, 1969 February 2 (Box 115, Folder 38)
- 1969 Stanford Research Institute, SRI Associates Day, 1969 December 11 (Box 115, Folder 39)